I you know so what are you asking me
right now?
>> Do you are you okay?
>> I can't answer questions about something
that I'm not aware of.
>> Okay. But are you okay with players kind
of expressing frustration over things
like that or is that something that you
hope that they kind of keep to
themselves? And
>> I I got to have more information before
I answer any of those kind of questions.
>> What conversations have you had with
Puka about his live stream this week?
>> Yeah, he was very apologetic. I don't
think he understood the totality of some
of the things. I think he issued that
apology. I know this guy's heart and for
anybody that was offended terribly sorry
about that. Um I know he feels that same
exact way. He's a young guy that's a
great kid that's continuing to learn
about, you know, just the platform that
he has. I love him. We're going to
continue to put our arm around him and
help him learn and grow. Uh but we never
want to do things that ever offend
anybody. And I know he feels that same
way.
>> How about them those guys coming into
onto your property at the facility in a
short week as you're preparing for the
biggest? Yeah, I I don't know anything
about that stuff. I I'm They came on our
property.
>> Hey, outside parking lot.
>> Cuz he said on the live stream that you
were mad.
>> I was I don't think No, that he did. He
say my name.
>> Oh, he said boss man.
>> Boss man. I assume that was he
>> wasn't me.
>> Yeah.
>> Did it feel like a distraction this
week?
>> No, it wasn't a distraction at all. Did
he Did you think his play showed that he
was distracted?
>> I didn't think so either. He went off
today. He He didn't. And you know what?
And I apologize for I'm you know what? I
love this team and man, when you put out
as much as our group does and you care
so much about something and you come up
short, it's incredibly disappointing. Um
but as it relates to just the things
that that you're asking, you know, we
always want to make sure that we handle
ourselves with class, learn from it.
I'll put my arm around him and continue
to educate our guys. I love this team. I
love his heart. I think he's going to
continue to grow and mature. Um, and I'm
going to be there right there with him
to continue to help do that. As far as
the other things, I know that that
wasn't a distraction. There was some
things that came up with you address it.
Um, and you keep it moving. And I think,
you know, most importantly, you never
want to offend anybody. And I know that
that's where his heart is as well. Um,
as far as the game's concerned, it was a
great back and forth battle between two
really good football teams. Um, what I
was referring to is is that I've never
quite seen anything like what happened
on the two-point conversion where you're
lined up to kickoff, then they say it's
a fumble because they had the clear and
obvious recovery. Now you tack it on,
you make it a 3030 game. Very
interesting. Didn't get a clear
explanation of everything that went on
just because of some of the timing of
it. They were trying to be able to do
that, but that's the thing that I've
said. I've never seen anything or never
been a part of anything like that. And
I've grown up around this game. I'm not
making excuses. is we don't do that. I
don't believe in that. It doesn't move
us forward. Uh but we do want clarity
and an understanding of, you know, the
things that we can do uh to minimize
that when we rejected the two-point
conversion. [clears throat]
>> Criticize the officials in the live
stream.
>> Yeah, we don't want to do that.
>> Criticize the officials in on Twitter
just now. Was that part of your
conversation with him after the live
stream?
>> No, I I have not spoken to him yet. So,
I just found out about that. We'll
continue to learn. I know you said
you'll put your arm around him and
you'll you'll talk through this with him
>> when he continues to do this stuff and
he's tweeting it after a game. Do you
feel like conversations are enough to
get it fixed or is there
>> Oh, yeah. It's going to get fixed. Trust
me on that. He He's responsible. He's
respectful and I'm going to continue to
help him grow and uh I'm with him every
step of the way. Thank you guys.
Appreciate it.
What was your reaction to the comments
that people made on the live?
>> Excuse me.
>> What were your What were your reaction
that made on the live stream?
>> To be honest with you, I'm going to tell
you the truth. I have not listened to it
or been a part of it. I understand that
he said some things that maybe he has
apologized for since then. Um, I have
not spent the time. This is a short week
for us and I've been grinding like crazy
to try to get the game ready. I'll
probably have a better comment for you
after I listen to it. um probably next
week or something like that. I just want
to be honest with you. Appreciate you
guys coming home.
>> It being a short week with a huge game.
>> Yeah. [clears throat]
>> Was that a distraction for you guys at
all in terms of
>> To be honest with you, you know, I I
didn't even have time to think about it.
Um I I obviously, you know, I don't want
to speak for him. Like I said, I haven't
I haven't listened to it or seen it or
whatever it is. Um uh you know, I just
know that I was focused as fast as much
as I could to get ready to play this
game as fast as I possibly could. I feel
like a lot of guys on our team were in
that boat. Um, you know, to try and do
that. Um, but I'll have more time to
look at it and give you guys a better
answer. Um, you know, later probably by
next week,
>> with Terrence Burton, just just what
does it mean for a rookie to have the
kind of game he did tonight and what
what does that do for a guy when you can
come into a game as big as this one and
have four pitches?
>> Yeah, I mean, I think a lot of guys on
our team had, you know, got experience
that they wouldn't have gotten, you
know. Um, you know, uh, I thought M did
a great job today. Um, Ferg was great.
Thought he scored on the one. I guess we
had a guy downfield. I have to take a
look at that one. Um, tough one there.
But, uh, no, I thought all those guys
played well. I thought Das did a great
job coming in when K went down. Um,
played really physical. I thought our
guys up front played great. Um, you
know, there's no secret to what we were
trying to do. Just smashmouth it and,
uh, you know, we ran the ball great.
We're able to throw up for some yards
and and some touchdowns as well. in the
mental and emotional es and flows of a
game. Sean [clears throat] said the
two-point conversion that you guys stop
was did that get can you guys is that
tougher?
>> No, you know, to be honest with you, I
I'd love I just want to know that rule
because I thought on plays like that
like two-minute play or two-point plays
inside of two minutes and stuff. I
didn't think you're allowed to advance a
fumble. Um, you know, otherwise I think
everybody would just go down. If you're
going down, just fumble it forward and
let somebody else advance. I don't know
the I obviously don't know the rule well
enough. They were um you know I'm sure
they talked to New York or whatever. Um
but that one was interesting to me. I'm
sure I'll get explanation. We'll get an
explanation and um but yeah, I mean you
just go play the next play. There was
plenty of football after that. Chances
to make plays and and do all that. So um
you know it was a play in the game. One
that I would love a little bit more you
know just uh you know explanation,
understanding of it and and once we do
that we'll move on. You're you're in the
playoffs, but obviously tonight's loss
may affect your opportunity to get the
number one seed. Is that challenging in
the next 11 days?
>> Go play. Where are we playing? Who we
playing? Put the ball down. Prepare. Go
play. That's the attitude this team's
had since day one. It's the attitude
we're going to have till the last game
we play this year. Uh listen, respect
everybody, fear nobody. Go play.
>> What were you being evaluated for in the
injury time?
Uh, I was not being evaluated for
anything.
>> Yep.
>> Why were you in pain?
>> I was uh I had to use the restroom. I
was didn't want to run in a couple more.
>> Matt, this team has responded well
following a loss. This is, you know, one
of the more dramatic ones. What do you
hope the team learns from this?
>> Oh, I mean, you know, just like every
game, you know, whether we win the game
or lose the game, there's plenty to
learn from. plenty of plays we'd love to
have back um you know in probably all
three phases. So, we're going to do what
we always do. Um you know, look at the
tape, find a way to you know, hey, tweak
a couple things to find a way to be
better, play for each other, and
continue to go out and play. Um that's
the best part about this team. Whether
we beat a team by 30 or we lose by one
on a last second play, um you know, this
team's as steady as it gets. So, I'm
proud to be a part of it. Proud of the
effort that we had together, you know,
had together today. and uh you know uh
tough one for sure, but uh we'll move on
and and you know, play who we got next.
>> Puka did finish with 225 yards. So with
[clears throat] no Devonte out on the
field, just how do you sum up the impact
and the ways that he was able to work
through a defense that's trying to take
him away?
>> Yeah, he was great. You know, he did a
great job. I thought our coaches did a
great job devising a plan to, you know,
just try to pick and choose our spots to
get him the ball. He made some big
plays. You know, when you make big
plays, that's how you get those yards.
Um, like I said earlier, I thought
really all the guys in our skill group
played really well and our guys up front
played well. So, um, you know, there are
a couple plays here and there we want
back for sure. Um, that's every game,
but anytime you come in here, um, play
that that defense, you know, uh, one of
the best, if not the best in the league,
and, um, you know, do what we were able
to do on offense, control the game, um,
you know, and, you know, score whatever
we scored, 37. Um, feel good about it.
Obviously, there's, you know, a couple
plays we want back to maybe score in the
red zone earlier in the game or continue
a drive where we got off the field early
in the game, but uh I was proud of our
effort of our entire team the way we
fought and clawed uh didn't go our way
tonight. Um continue to play. That's
what we're going to do. Matthew, just
kind of along those lines in terms of,
you know, the adjustments the offensive
staff and the offense as a whole. I
mean, from the first time you guys
played this defense and, you know, the
way you produced and moved the ball
tonight, just what do you like about
those adjustments and the game plan
overall?
>> Yeah, I just uh you know, we were on the
field a little bit more, so we were able
to affect the game. Uh, and like I've
said in our, you know, conference or our
chat on Wednesday or whatever day that
was, normally a Wednesday. Sorry, I'm
lost. But um but you know, our defense
did such a good job of giving us short
fields last time. It was kind of a weird
game where you didn't get to feel like,
hey, we're in the flow of what we want
to do on first and second down and then
on third down and and um so the first
time we played him was a little bit that
way. Um but we just played aggressive,
tried to keep the ball in play.
Obviously, uh you know, can do a little
bit better job on some of those. Um but
uh you know, I thought our guys did
great run the football. our guys up
front were were uh doing a great job and
and then when we you know called pass
plays uh you know we made some
explosives and then you know checked it
down a few times when they did a nice
job covering it. So um it was just a
good mix. I thought Sean called a great
game. We obviously had a great plan and
and um you know continue to build on it.
>> Okay. Thank you.